https://coda.org/privacy/

Search
Search for:
Search
Search for:
Privacy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Co-Dependents Anonymous collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.coda.org website (“Site”).
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Nonpersonal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Co-Dependents Anonymous may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our Site
We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.
To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more
efficiently.
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may
also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Electronic newsletters
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Changes to this privacy policy
Co-Dependents Anonymous has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we
are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. Contacting us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
CoDA, Fellowship Services Office
PO Box 33577
Phoenix, AZ 85067-3577
P: +1 (602) 277-7991
+1 (888) 444-2359 {Toll free}
+1 (888) 444-2379 {Spanish toll free}
This document was last updated on September 07, 2016
Quick Meeting Search:
5 Miles10 Miles20 Miles30 Miles40 Miles50 Miles100 Miles200 Miles
FIND MEETING
CONTACT
Fellowship Services OfficePO Box 33577Phoenix, AZ 85067-3577
+1 (602) 277-7991
+1 (888) 444-2359
(Toll Free)
+1 (888) 444-2379
(Spanish)
ABOUT CoDAWhat is Codependence?
Get on a mailing list:
Choose from the following lists:
©CoDA.org, All Rights Reserved.
Fair Use
Privacy
To update an existing meeting, CLICK HERE, search for the meeting ID,
Click to the meeting and use the link “UPDATE THIS MEETING”, found under the map of the meeting.
X
